Joseph Rohman

Technical Project Manager

I am a certified fullstack software engineer, with a degree in Advertising, and proven experience as a highly-effective and efficient project manager. I seek out challenges and I have a passion for innovation in both business and product design.

Work History

2019-03 -Current

Freelance Web Developer

JHRohman, Daly City, California

- Projects: tractu.com, celestepharma.com, josephrohman.com
- Successfully creates websites leveraging user-focus design and brand marketing strategies
- Full-stack developer with primary languages: React, HTML, CSS, & Javascript, and secondary languages Python/Django, Node.js
- Experience with MongoDB, Heroku, Postgres, & SQL

2015-06 -Current

Freelance CAD Drafter

JHRohman, Daly City, California

- Projects: Blueprint Studios Sephora conference 2018 & 2019, San Francisco Symphony 2018 & 2019
- Superior knowledge of design and production process
- Working closely with clients or team members to turn vague ideas into full production-ready products
- Consistently generates build-documents and 3D renderings that can be understood by anyone, of any discipline, or speaking any language

2011-06 -Current

Freelance Graphic Designer

JHRohman, Daly City, California

- Projects: Tractu Pharma LLC, Celeste Pharma LLC, Bits & Pieces
- Creative & Art director, graphic designer, brand marketer
- Succeeding in translating complex ideas & motivations into compelling, modern designs
- Leveraging Advertising degree & design background to spearhead client marketing projects
- Effectively collaborates with wide range of individuals from designers to executives

2017-06 -2019-02

Project Manager

Blueprint Studios, San Bruno, CA

 Directed the department of 15 people, managed 50 vendors, supporting all other departments, and

Personal Info

Address

San Francisco Bay Area, California, 94014

E-mail

josephhrohman@gmail.com

WWW

josephrohman.com

Skills

Leadership

Time Management

Trello

Public Speaking

Risk Management

Github

HTML5, CSS3, Javascript ES6, React.js

Rhino 5 3D CAD Software

Adobe Creative Suite

Business Development

Brand Marketing

Advanced problem solving

Strategic planning

Operations management

Project management

Graphic design

Market analysis

- completing over 600 events in 2 years
- Created automated record & scheduling system, giving department back 25% of our time, increasing the transparency of budgeting, and increasing the accuracy of project forecast
- Orchestrated departmental business development, interfacing with clients such as Google, Adobe, and Facebook
- Risk Manager; the go-to person to call for solutions across all production departments and client crises. Was requested to be on company 'think-tank' for crisis resolution

Education

2013-08 -

2016-12 University of San Francisco - San Francisco, CA
2019-03 - Certification: Fullstack Software Engineering
2019-06 General Assembly San Francisco - San Francisco, CA

Bachelor of Arts: Advertising